import { ILessonQuestion } from '../services/lesson.service';

export const PHONETICS_QUESTIONS: Map<string, ILessonQuestion[]> = new Map<string, ILessonQuestion[]>([
  ['1', [
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ch', answer: 'Ch.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'kh', answer: 'Kh.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'gh', answer: 'Gh.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ng', answer: 'Nh.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ngh', answer: 'Ngh.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'th', answer: 'Th.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'nh', answer: 'Nh.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'tr', answer: 'Tr.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ph', answer: 'Ph.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'gi', answer: 'Gi.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'qu', answer: 'Qu.m4a' },
  ]],
  ['2', [
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ia', answer: 'ia.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ua', answer: 'ua.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ưa', answer: 'uwa.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ao', answer: 'ao.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'eo', answer: 'eo.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'au', answer: 'au.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'âu', answer: 'aau.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'iu', answer: 'iu.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ưu', answer: 'uwu.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ai', answer: 'ai.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'oi', answer: 'oi.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ôi', answer: 'ooi.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ơi', answer: 'owi.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ui', answer: 'ui.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ưi', answer: 'uwi.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ay', answer: 'ay.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ây', answer: 'aay.m4a' },
  ]],
  ['3', [
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ac', answer: 'ac.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'âc', answer: 'aac.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ăc', answer: 'awc.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'oc', answer: 'oc.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ôc', answer: 'ooc.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'uc', answer: 'uc.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ưc', answer: 'wc.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'at', answer: 'at.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ăt', answer: 'awt.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ât', answer: 'aat.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'et', answer: 'et.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'êt', answer: 'eet.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'it', answer: 'it.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ot', answer: 'ot.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ôt', answer: 'oot.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ơt', answer: 'owt.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ut', answer: 'ut.m4a' },
    { question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a', lessonUnit: 'ưt', answer: 'wt.m4a' },
  ]]
]);
